Analyzing exammmm.pdf
Page 1 Sample Text Start:
  
  
  1. What  biomedical technicians or biomedical engineers do ?
  
  a) Plan, select, manage, and repair medical devices and technologies
  b) Ensure a high standard of performance of medical devices and systems through
  preventive maintenance (PM) or corrective maintenance (CM) checks or quality
  inspections
  c) Provide clinical staff with on-call technical assistance and device training
  d) Help facilities provide safe, cost-effective, and well-maintained healthcare technologies
  that improve clinical outcomes
  e) Only A and B are TRUE
  f) A,B,C,D are TRUE
  g) A,B,C,D are FALSE
  
  2. The service life cycle of medical equipment is characterized by:
  
  a) Date of reception of medical equipment , maintenance review date of medical equipment
  ,Serial number of equipment , names of manufacturer ,lifespan of equipment
  ,maintenance cost  and purchasing Price of an equipment .
